[Song] I'm the
branding and communication officer
for FWD Insurance.
[Song] I
have to say there are several factors that...
Make our brand a success every day.   What I
want to highlight is the aspect of
stability. We have a very strong strategy
because it aligns with
our vision and our core working principle, which is
customer-oriented. Beyond that, I must
mention our strategy for building our brand.
Yes, we are different from others because we...   It
's the only brand that focuses on
inspiration, emphasizing brand building in a positive way.   Plus,
we're in continuous communication.
Because across all channels, consumers have a
preconceived notion about us in this regard.
[Song]
Regarding the economic challenges, I
must say that our forwarding team has also experienced problems.
Like everyone else, but what...   What
we do is we monitor the situation closely.   We're getting
closer, and we're making some adjustments.
Our Gigi style is to develop products
and services to help our customers.   It's for
us, to get through these difficult times together.
[Song]
We want to be at the top of the list for
consumers. We want
FWD insurance to be the first name that comes to mind for Thai people.
[Song] I
must say, I feel very honored.   We
won the Superband award this time.
Because it's a mine that serves as proof...   The
success in what we have done so far, and the...   The
entire team has always been committed to
giving more than 100%, and
receiving the Super Brand award has further enhanced our commitment.
We need to strive for 200-300% effort to
offer the best to Thai consumers.
And she continues to maintain the standards of Superman.
[Song]